The red carpet program is really
exciting. It enables us to take
concepts, ideas and translate them into
reality that our clients can actually
use. The biggest challenge is getting
started. Where do you start? Pick an
idea, go with it. You need to go through
that process in order to be um
competitive in the future. biggest
learning that other partners are also
struggling a lot with use cases and are
in the same position as us. We can now
approach problems with AI. It's not the
technical thing, it's the envisioning.
>> So our biggest learnings so far have
been really the prompt engineering and
the time that it takes to do that as
well as testing
test. It's the biggest challenge in
building an effective co-pilot function.
It requires continuous testing to make
sure that you have the best prompt for
co-pilot to deliver the best answers for
your customers. It's also important to
have automated test in place to ensure
that in the future your co-pilot
function works just as you envisioned it
in the start.
Most important thing to consider when
building co-pilot is working together as
a team and really make it a focused
effort for your organization. just
start, take small steps and then grow.